Before Scooby-Doo these B.F.F.s had a clue.
Daphne & Velma is a comedy, horror, action film directed by Suzi Yoonessi.
Before their eventual team-up with Scooby and the gang, bright and optimistic Daphne and whip-smart and analytical
Velma are both mystery-solving teens who are best friends but have only met online - until now.
Daphne has just transferred to Velma's school, Ridge Valley High, an incredible tech-savvy institute with
all the latest gadgets provided by the school's benefactor, tech billionaire Tobias Bloom.
And while competition is fierce among the students for a coveted internship at Bloom Innovative, Daphne and Velma dig beyond all the gadgets and tech
to investigate what is causing some of the brightest students in school to disappear - only to emerge again in a zombie-fied state.
Daphne, played by Sarah Jeffery.
Velma, played by Sarah Gilman.
Carol, played by Vanessa Marano.
Mikayla Martin, played by Courtney Dietz.
Griffin Griffiths, played by Evan Castelloe.
Nedley Blake, played by Brian Stepanek.
Daphne & Velma is a 2018 American direct-to-video comedy
mystery film directed by Suzi Yoonessi.
The film is the fifth overall installment to the Scooby-Doo live-action film series and a spin-off prequel to the film
series and the whole Scooby-Doo franchise, featuring the title characters Daphne Blake and Velma Dinkley.
The film is produced by Ashley and Jennifer Tisdale's Blondie
Girl Productions along with Blue Ribbon Content.
It premiered at the Chicago Comic & Entertainment Expo (C2E2) on April 7, 2018, and was
released on DVD, Blu-ray, and Digital HD on May 22, 2018, by Warner Bros.
Home Entertainment.
The film explores themes of high school, based on
cartoon, spin off, young detective.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.